mygirlfund.com 2013-09-09

# MyGirlFund: Privacy Policy

MyGirlFund.com (hereinafter referred to as “MyGirlFund.com” or the “Website”).

THIS PRIVACY POLICY GOVERNS YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, WHICH IS PROVIDED BY MGF, THE OWNER OF THE WEBSITE. BY ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE INDICATING YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE BY MGF AT ANY TIME IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE AFTER SUCH CHANGES ARE IMPLEMENTED CONSTITUTES YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF THE CHANGES. PLEASE CONSULT THIS PRIVACY POLICY REGULARLY.

NOTE: Our privacy policy is null and void in cases of fraud!

This policy explains the privacy practices for MGF LLC, a Delaware limited liability company and owner of the Website, (hereinafter referred to as “MGF LLC”, “MGF”, “our”, “we”, or “us”). In order to provide interactive computer billing and avoid fraud, MGF collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you can interact with MGF in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use.

## 1) Information Collection:

Visitors can access our Website home page and browse certain public areas of our Website without disclosing any personal data. However, in order to provide you with a particular product or service online, MGF may request that you voluntarily supply MGF with primary personal data (such as name, address, telephone number and email address) and identifiers (such as Website password). MGF gives you the option of using a secure transmission method for sending such information.

MGF receives and stores all information that you enter in our Website and billing pages. In addition, MGF collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address, and MGF employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. Additionally, when becoming a Member of the Website, MGF uses an outside service to verify that you are over 18 years old. You are required to provide MGF with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide MGF with such information could result in voiding your Agreement with MGF.

You can inquire about your personal data by sending an e-mail to customerservice@MyGirlFund.com. Within a week, MGF shall provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which MGF keeps about you. MGF charges a $25 processing fee for the request. Prior to completing your request, MGF may require that you provide MGF with proof of your identity. MGF reserves the right to refuse any request for information though MGF will communicate the reason for its decision.

## 2) Information Use:

MGF is the sole owner of the information collected on its sites. MGF will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this policy. MGF shall release data when required by law, to enforce its Agreement or the contract rights of its clients. MGF shares the following data with the owner/operator of the Website from which you are purchasing goods and services utilizing MGF services: the URL you are purchasing goods or services from, your e-mail address, your name, your address, your phone number, your date of birth, and your agreement to be bound by MGF terms and conditions. MGF uses the data it collects for the technical administration of the Website, research and development, and fraud deterrence.

## 3) Information sharing:

MGF does not rent, sell and/or share information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies, except that we may provide information about you under the following circumstances:

  * A. MGF provides the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MGF under confidentiality agreements. These companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * B. MGF responds to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise MGF's legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * C. MGF believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Website's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law; and/or,
  * D. MGF transfers information about you if MGF is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MGF will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

## 4) Email correspondence:

MGF may request a confirmation when you receive and open an e-mail communication delivered by MGF. We archive and identify the origination IP address of all email sent into our network.

## 5) Third party information:

Occasionally, MGF receives information from third parties to compare it to information that you had provided to MGF for fraud prevention purposes.

## 6) Cookies:

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. MGF employs “cookie” technology. We use Cookie to store personal data, to authenticate you as a Site user, for security purposes, and to track our affiliate click-throughs and sign-up rate.

## 7) Children:

MGF does not request, or knowingly collect, personal data from anyone under the age of 18. Furthermore, MGF does not knowingly give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our Website.

## 8) Security:

We take every precaution to protect our visitors' information. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, or accidental loss. MGF utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. MGF encrypts the information that you provided.

In addition, MGF does everything to protect your information off-line. All employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. MGF employs a username and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and third parties.

## 9) Correction/Updating Personal Information:

You may access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. You may request to access your information by sending a request to:

> Administrator  
>  Consumer Protection Dept.  
>  MGF LLC.  
>  3525 Del Mar Heights Rd. #206  
>  San Diego, CA 92130  
>  or e-mail: [support@mygirlfund.com](mailto:support@mygirlfund.com).

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at the above address.
